我们是宝石战士
We are the Crystal Gems
本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
终日拯救世界
we'll always save the day
如果你感到怀疑
and if you think we can't
■
时间轴： 树叶
我们总能找到出路
we'll always find a way
■
翻译： 阿珩
所以全世界人们都信任
that's why the people of this world believe in...
■
校订： 树叶
石榴  紫晶
Garnet, Amethyst...
和珍珠
and Pearl...
还有史蒂文
and Steven!
宇宙小子  第二季第六集
Steven Universe  S02E06  Shirt Club
T恤俱乐部
■
后期： 树叶  小黑
珍珠  紫晶  石榴
Pearl?! Amethyst?! Garnet?!
你不用喊那么大声  史蒂文  我们就在这儿呢
You don't have to yell, Steven. We're right here.
我知道  但是我刚画完了这张画
I know, but I finished this drawing, and I
想要给你们看看
wanted to show it to you.
-当然  -好的
- Oh! Uh, of course. - All right!
吉他老爸教你弹吉他
Guitar Dad teaches you guitar!
-这是什么  -这是我爸爸
- What is that? - It's my dad!
他要开始教吉他课
He's going to start teaching guitar lessons
他还让我做公关部负责人
and he made me his P.R. department.
-他嘴里的东西是什么  -那些是他的牙齿
- What's that stuff in his mouth? - Those are his teeth.
这些闪电是什么
What are the lightning bolts for?
至于那个  我只想表现出
well, I-I was trying to show
我爸爸弹吉他真的很赞  而且
that dad really rocks on the guitar, and ...
那么应该有石头从吉他里蹦出来
Then there should be rocks falling out of the guitar.
我听到你说的了  但是提醒得太晚了
I hear what you're saying, but it's too late for notes.
这马克笔擦不掉
This is permanent marker.
这个可爱的传单是干什么的  史蒂文
What's that cute flyer for, Steven?
这是给我爸爸做的  他可以教你弹吉他
It's for my dad! He'll teach you guitar.
你们想报名吗  我爸爸真的很棒
You guys want to sign up? My dad's really good!
我可能会顺路过去看看
Maybe I'll stop by and check it out.
来  给你一张传单
Here, let me give you a flyer and ...
-欢迎光临大甜甜圈  -嗨  巴克
- Welcome to the big donut! - Hey, Buck!
什么  巴克  巴克  巴——————克
Oh! What? Buck, Buck, Bu-u-u-u-ck!
哈哈  你最近过得如何啊
Ha ha! What's going on, man?
你今天想点些什么
What can we get for you today?
我能要一份卡普里沙拉吗
Can I get a caprese salad?
抱歉  巴克  我们只卖甜甜…
Oh, sorry, Buck, we only serve don..
别担心  巴克
.Do-nut worry, Buck!
我会给你做一份沙拉的...很容易做  我马上就回来
I'll whip you up a salad ... no sweat! I'll be right back!
拉尔斯  我们这连蔬菜都没有
Lars, we don't even have vegetables here!
吉他老爸是什么
Heh, what's a Guitar Dad?
你喜欢我的传单吗  是给我爸爸做的
Like my flyer? It's for my dad!
他可以教你弹吉他
He'll teach you guitar!
来  你也拿一张吧
Here, take one of these with you!
准确地说  是贴一张在身上
Actually, just wear it!
-你怕痒吗  -这可以做一件非常棒的T恤  老兄
- Are you ticklish? - This would make a rad shirt, man.
-真的吗  -是啊  我们来把传单印成T恤吧
- Really? - Yeah! Let's make your flyer into T-shirts!
噢天  我爸爸会爱死这个的
Oh, man! My dad would love that!
来击个掌
Gimme five on it.
你没碰到
Oh, you missed.
你能回归家族事业真是太好了  儿子
Ho! I think it's swell you're returning to the family business, son!
你要帮老爸再一次连任吗
Gonna help the old man get re-elected again, eh?
噢  儿子
Aw, son!
这不是为了竞选  老爸
It's not for campaign stuff, dad.
史蒂文和我是在创作艺术
Steven and I are making art.
艺术啊
Art!
艺术吗  我反正理解不了
Art, huh? I don't understand it myself,
但是一个男孩必须得有兴趣和追求
but a boy's got to have interests and ambitions!
这些东西可以用来做T恤吗
This stuff can be used to make T-shirts?
是的  我这里有最新的  专业级的
Oh, yeah, I've got all the latest, state-of-the-art
丝网印刷设备  多年以来都用于
screen-printing equipment from years of
竞选和一些类似的市长相关业务
campaigning and other some-such mayorly things.
比如这周  我打算要纪念一张长椅
Like this week, I'm commemorating a bench!
欢迎来到长椅市  真不错啊
"Welcome to... 'Bench' City"? Thrifty!
-老爸  你不能用这个  -为什么不能
- Dad, you can't use this! - Why not?
你懂的  我要拿下年轻人的选票  儿砸
You know, I got to "gank dat" youth vote, boyeeee!
-老爸  够了  -这是什么
- Dad, stop. - What's this?
你发现什么了
What have you got there?
我有好多年都没见过这个了
I haven't seen this in years!
还记得你画这幅画的时候吗  巴克
Remember when you drew this, Buck?
你迫不及待地把这幅画炫耀给其他小朋友们看
You couldn't wait to show it off to all your little montessori friends.
好了老爸  谢谢你的帮助
Okay, dad! Thanks for all your help.
-回头见  -好吧  孩子
- See you later! Bye. - All right, kids!
我是说中东和平  福尔摩斯
I mean, peace in the Middle East, Holmes!
太酷了
So cool.
我们快点开始吧
Let's just get started already.
-真棒  -现在每个人都会想上我老爸的课了
- Swag.  - Now everyone's gonna want lessons from dad!
这可比你爸爸的事更伟大  史蒂文  这是艺术
This is bigger than your dad, Steven. It's art.
它会强烈地冲击公众的意识
And it's gonna flood the public consciousness.
那我们快开始派发这些吧
Well, let's start handing them out!
太普通了  我们要引发争议
Too simple. We need to get controversial.
我们需要创造  一个爆炸性事件
We need to create ... Boom! ... a scene.
搜寻目标
Scanning for targets.
T恤加农炮填装完毕
T-shirt cannon loaded and ready!
发现酸奶油
Sour Cream sighted!
做好准备  瞄准
Get ready! Take aim!
然后
And..
这是什么
What in the world?
这是所有击中过我脑袋的东西中
Oh, this is the coolest thing
最酷的一件了
I've ever been hit in the head with!
发现罗纳尔多  瞄准
Ronaldo spotted. Take aim!
什么鬼东西
Whoa! What the heck?! Huh?
哇哦  不可思议
Whoa! Weird!
某种外星太空老爹吉他T恤
Some kind of extraterrestrial space dad guitar shirt?
所以  你终于决定要进行首次联络了吗
So, you've finally decided to make first contact, huh?
你在哪
Where are you?!
发现拉尔斯  瞄准
Lars sighted. Take aim!
我了个  这是什么垃圾
Youch! What the... What is this garbage?
是巴克做的吗
Buck made this?
真搞笑  谢啦  巴克
This is hilarious! Thanks, Buck!
干杯
Cheers!
巴克  这真是个好主意
Buck, this was such a good idea!
搞不懂为什么以前我们没有合作过
I don't know why we didn't collaborate on a project sooner!
这会让我爸爸超级开心的
This will make my dad so happy!
我都等不及想看到待会儿见他时他脸上的表情了
I can't wait to see the look on his face when I stop by later.
是的  应该挺能引人发笑
Yeah. Should be good for a laugh.
为什么是引人发笑
Huh? Why would it be good for a ...
-姑娘  看看我的新T恤  -真可爱
- Girl! Check out my new shirt! - It's really cute!
-哪来的  -不知道
- Where'd you get it? - I don't know.
我外出散步的时候 它刚好掉在我面前
It just landed in front of me when I was out walking.
好吧  如果我是你  就不会穿刚刚从天上掉下来的T恤
Well, if I were you, I wouldn't wear some random shirt that just fell out of the sky.
要是里面有虫子怎么办
What if there were bugs in it?
别紧张  谁在意它是哪来的
Relax! Who cares where it came from?
这件T恤是我这辈子见过最有意思的东西了
This shirt is the funniest thing I've seen in my life!
看起来我们的T恤起到效果了
Looks like our shirt has a really good buzz going.
是啊  但我觉得他们只是把它当个玩笑
Yeah, but I think they think it's a joke.
唯一重要的事
Heh. The only thing that's important
是她们在谈论它
is that they're talking about it.
-真正的艺术就是如此  -好吧  我想你是对的
- That's how real art works. - Oh, well, I-I guess you're right.
-你看这样如何  -哈哈  太糟了
- Uh, how's this? - Ha ha ha. So bad.
好了  让我们开始第一堂课吧
Okay! Let's get started with the first lesson!
坐下  然后拿一把…  你要去哪儿
Have a seat and grab a ... Where you going?
他可能刚收到一条重要的短信什么的
Oh, uh, I guess he got an important text or something.
-今天状况怎么样  -棒极了
- How's it been going today? - Really great!
好多人来过了  多亏了你的T恤  孩子
Lots of people have been coming by, thanks to your T-shirts, little guy.
真是太好了  爸爸
That's great, dad!
-我很高兴能帮上忙  - 耶  吉他老爸
- I'm really glad I could help ... - Yoo-hoo! Guitar Dad!
我就是想说  我觉得你很棒很搞笑
I just wanted to say I think you're wonderful and hilarious!
谢谢
Uh... thank you?
感觉有点怪怪的
Huh. That's kind of strange.
-哪里奇怪  -很多人路过这里
- What is? - Well, lots of people have stopped by
但都没有上课
but no one's taken a lesson yet.
-什么  真的吗  - 他们可能只是
- What? Really?! - Ah, maybe they're just
先过来看看情况
checking out the scene before
然后再来正式上课
they come back to get a real lesson!
-巴克  -我最重要的兄弟来了
- Buck! - Hey, there's my main man.
那些T恤没起作用  巴克
The shirts aren't working, Buck!
当然起作用了  人们都爱它
Yeah, they are. People love 'em.
但没有人去上我爸爸的吉他课
But nobody wants guitar lessons from my dad!
-这不是重点  -那什么才是重点啊
- That's not the point. - What?! Then what is the point?
重点是  这T恤超级棒
The point is, it's an amazing shirt.
我画画没有那么好啦
Aw, my drawing's not that good.
-确实 你画的很烂  -什么
- Yeah, no. It's terrible. - What?!
这就是它的优异之处  你的作品很纯真
That's what's so great about it. Your work is so naive.
你真的很爱你爸爸
You really love your dad.
有意思
It's funny.
我  不想再做这些T恤了
I... I don't want to make these shirts anymore.
不行史蒂文  它这么受欢迎  你不能阻止
Too bad, Steven. It's so current, you can't stop it.
我是品味的制造者  我要继续制造流行品味
I'm a taste maker, and I'm gonna keep making tastes...
-直到永远  -永远吗
- forever. - Forever?
-是的 在我参加完我爸爸差劲的长椅纪念式之后
Well, forever, after I go to my dad's lame bench commemoration.
以和为贵
Peace.
-石榴  珍珠  紫晶  -史蒂文
- Garnet! Pearl! Amethyst! - Steven!
-怎么了  -哪儿着火啦
- What is it?! - Whoa, where's the fire?!
事态紧急
It's an emergency!
你们得帮我摆脱掉所有的T恤
You have to help me get rid of all the shirts
还要阻止巴克制做更多
and stop Buck from making more!
难道是那些T恤活了  并且
Have the shirts come to life and
-控制了穿着它们的人吗  -不是的 它们…
- possessed the bodies of their wearers? - No, they just ...
人们穿上那些神奇的T恤身上会着火吗
Are people catching on fire when they put on the magic shirts?
不是  它们只是…
No, no, th-they're just ...
难道那些T恤会摧毁穿着的人的意志
Are the shirts destroying the wearers' wills
让人们生无可恋吗
to continue on in this mortal coil,
从而让海滩市关闭吗
thereby shutting down Beach City?!
都不是  它们只是
No!! They're... They're just
未经我同意使用了我的艺术创作
using my art in a way I don't agree with.
那我们就管不着了
Eh, we'll pass.
什么  但我真的需要你们的帮助啊
What?! But... But, I really need your help!
史蒂文  听上去这是一个很抽象的问题
Steven, this sounds like a very abstract problem.
没法靠打架解决
It's not something we can punch.
你必须学会帮助自己  这样才能变强
You must learn to help yourself. That's how you become stronger.
-说的很对  -一点没错
- Good point, good point. - Oh, absolutely.
-但是  -你想想办法  史蒂文
- But! - You'll figure something out, Steven!
是的  为什么不重新用那些解决冲突的方法呢
Yes, why not dust off those conflict-resolution skills!
先了解你的问题是什么
Let your problem be known.
然后再努力理解它
Then you can work towards an understanding.
噢  我会让他理解的
Oh, I'll make him understand.
我会让他们都理解的
I'll make them all understand!
他不会有事的
Eh, he'll be fine.
好了  每个人都到了吗
Okay. Is everyone here?
大家好  我应该写一篇演讲稿
Hello! I was supposed to write a speech
以纪念这张  新的长椅  但是
to, um, commemorate this, uh, new bench, but
事实是  我用光了我家里的
what had happened was I ran out of printer ink in
打印机的油墨
my printer that I keep at home.
所以我去了商店  你们猜怎么
So, I went to the store and wouldn't you know it?
他们那没有我要买的牌子  所以...
They didn't carry the brand I was looking for, so...
-再见  -我给一个哥们打了电话
- Bye! - ...I called up a buddy of
他欠我一些
mine who owed me a few
政治方面的好处  但是他不在家
political favors, and he wasn't home!
小心
Look out!
不
No!
我被...T恤击中了
I've been... shirt!
巴克... 这是你做的吗
Buck... did you make this?
这件T恤简直是神作
This shirt is genius!
这比吉他老爸有趣多了
This is way funnier than Guitar Dad!
这张长椅的确挺舒服的
This bench is actually pretty comfortable.
今天有人过来上课吗
Anyone else stop by for lessons today?
目前还没有  但是我确信明天会有起色的
So far, no, but, I'm sure it'll pick up tomorrow!
是啊  一定会   顺便这个是给你的
Yeah, I'm sure it will. This is for you, by the way.
这是最后一件  所以是超级限量版
This is the last one, so it's super-limited edition!
太贴心了  谢谢  史蒂文
Aw, sweet! Thanks, Steven!
史蒂文  我就是想说  我很抱歉
Yo, Steven, just wanted to say, uh, I'm sorry for what
-我做了那样的事  -没关系  巴克
- I did and uh... - It's okay, Buck.
你不用再说别的了
You don't have to say any more than that.
你真是个很酷的家伙  史蒂文·宇宙
You're a cool cat, Steven Universe.
你好  宇先生
Hey, Mister "U."?
你想和我拍张照吗  还是别的什么
You want to take a picture with me or some junk?
没门  伙计
No way, man.
我想上课  吉他老爸的课
I want a lesson... from Guitar Dad!